ADAPTED FROM DEMON KING
OF JINJIANG LITERATURE CITY
ORIGINAL WORK BY JIULU FEIXIANG
Legend has it
that in order to learn
ancient mystique techniques,
Dongfang Qingcang,
the Moon Supreme of the Moon Tribe,
became a monster
without any feelings.
He killed his father,
took the position of Moon Supreme,
and led 100,000 soldiers of the Moon Tribe
to burn, kill, and loot.
The Fairy Realm Shuiyuntian,
the Moon Tribe Cangyan Sea,
and the Mortal World Yunmeng Lake
were in grave danger.
In order to save the common people,
Lady Chidi, God of War of Fairy Realm,
even destroyed her primordial spirit
to die with Dongfang Qingcang
and sealed the 100,000 demon soldiers
of the Moon Tribe.
But the primordial spirit
of Dongfang Qingcang
cannot be destroyed.
Once he is resurrected,
the three realms will be in danger again.
Legend has it
that only the Goddess of Xishan
can defuse this catastrophe.
But she
disappeared.
YUJING, SHUIYUNTIAN
ARBITER HALL, SHUIYUNTIAN
FAIRY ORCHID
I'm Orchid,
a fairy.
These are not ordinary leaves.
They're Destiny Books.
Every leaf tells the fate of a person.
And my duty
is to organize
and take care of these books.
Don't worry.
We won't interfere in anyone's fate.
My master is Arbiter,
a high immortal
in charge of the Destiny Book.
She is not only my master
but also my boss.
Our relationship is like
a shopkeeper
and shop assistant in the Mortal World.
In front of misfortune,
deities and humans
can do nothing.
We can do nothing.
This unlucky orchid
is me.
Since she accidentally spoiled
my immortal root with wine,
my cultivation and power
have always been bad.
After teaching me the skills,
my master left for the Mortal World
and hasn't come back for 500 years.
Even though
I'm a little lonely
in Arbiter Hall alone,
life
isn't bad.
I'm getting better
at repairing Destiny Books.
I never burn the midnight oil.
And there's not much to clean,
so I'm not tired.
The flowers have enlightened their wisdom,
so they can chat with me.
Don't sleep.
Only by cultivating hard can you become
a fairy like me soon.
What time is it? Let me sleep more.
What's so good about being like you?
You do so much work.
It's better to be a plant.
The other fairies
also treat me well.
You even took the portrait
of Lord Changheng.
You are so shameless.
No one bullies me.
Even we can't talk to Lord Changheng.
Lord Changheng will
never look at you in this life.
I plan to take the immortal examination
and go to Fountain Palace
to repay Lord Changheng.
What is Orchid looking at?
What else?
Her Lord Changheng.
That portrait is torn.
Why does she look at that all day?
What does Lord Changheng look like?
Why is Orchid so fascinated?
He is the God of War, a bigwig.
How can we see him?
Then how exactly did Lord Changheng
become her savior?
Could this be a dream of Orchid?
Repairing Destiny Books is not hard
but cumbersome.
A man's fate
can be affected by any minor things.
A small discrepancy can make
a great difference.
It's even more complicated
in my master's words.
One's destiny comes from natural law.
- Everything is a circulation of karma.
- Karma in the past
- Natural law and karma
- and everything now
- will never be depleted.
- will result in the future.
I can repair 50 books a day,
1,500 each month.
After I repair 50,000 of them,
I'll write a letter of resignation
to Master.
By then,
Lord Changheng, my savior,
should be back.
YUNZHONG WATER PAVILION, SHUIYUNTIAN
Lord Yunzhong.
GOD OF WAR, CHANGHENG
SHUIYUNTIAN EMPEROR, LORD YUNZHONG
Changheng.
You regained lost ground
in the Northernmost Ocean
and defeated Xunfeng,
the leader of the Moon Tribe.
You helped pacify the rebellion.
What reward do you want?
The Moon Tribe was already divided.
They were just a disorderly mob.
It's my duty to quell the rebellion.
I dare not take credit.
Lord Changheng is too modest.
Yes.
Although Xunfeng
is far weaker
than the deceased Dongfang Qingcang,
he is the top threat to Shuiyuntian now.
Lord Changheng seriously hurt
Xunfeng's vitality this time.
His contribution is immeasurable.
Even if Dongfang Qingcang
were still alive,
I would kill him too.
However,
as the Northernmost Ocean
just settled down,
there are still many affairs to do.
I wonder
why you recalled me back to Yujing.
HAOTIAN TOWER, SHUIYUNTIAN
Trepidation from Haotian Tower?
Do you still remember Dongfang Qingcang?
Of course.
Thirty thousand years ago,
Dongfang Qingcang was killed by immortals.
But what does he have to do
with Haotian Tower?
You were young at that time,
so you're not aware.
Although immortals got together
to kill him,
his body was still preserved
and his primordial spirit was intact.
My father could only
secretly seal him in Haotian Tower
with the help of the immortals.
To avoid panic in Shuiyuntian,
this became a secret
that only a few high immortals knew.
That day,
Lord Dong trapped his soul and body
and led immortals
to set thousands of seals
in Haotian Tower.
It was called Haotian Matrix.
This matrix has gathered
all the immortals' power.
In terms of strength,
no one in the three realms can destroy it.
Then why is there trepidation
with Haotian Tower?
Although Dongfang Qingcang
is unconscious,
his primordial spirit is still powerful.
It pounded every day
and actually loosened the seal.
If his primordial spirit
goes out of the tower,
the three realms will be in danger.
My father is still in seclusion.
So I called you back
to strengthen the seal
with the help of all high immortals.
Yes.
ARBITER HALL, SHUIYUNTIAN
This is the 42,699th.
I'm almost there.
I'm coming.
ARBITER HALL
As a peach blossom spirit,
you do nothing all day.
Does it take that long to answer the door?
I'm not a peach blossom.
I am an orchid.
And I have things to do.
High Immortal Buyusi
wants to check the Destiny Books.
Hurry up.
LIANG SHENG, DU RUO,
LIANG XUE, AN GE, CHUAN MING
What an unlucky day.
Lord Changheng returns victoriously today
and we're not able to welcome him.
We're sent to such a remote place instead
to get Destiny Books.
These are the Destiny Books you want.
Wait.
Excuse me.
Did you say
that Lord Changheng is back?
Why are you asking about that?
You're a Bengal rose
with a damaged immortal root.
Do your chores.
Don't ask nonsense.
Let's go.
They always act this way.
If Master were here,
you wouldn't dare to be this way.
ARBITER HALL
This is great!
Lord Changheng is back early.
I'm going to pick
a basket of the most beautiful flowers
and bring them to Fountain Palace.
Orchid.
Does Lord Changheng remember who you are?
That's why I should dress up
and give Lord Changheng a good impression.
SHUYU FOREST, SHUIYUNTIAN
Lord Changheng.
Orchid. Be graceful.
Bear what I told you in mind.
You should appear gentle,
enchanting, and gorgeous.
Only then will he remember you.
Thank…
Thank you, Lord Changheng.
Wait.
These flowers
are for you.
There's no need.
It's my duty to kill the enemy.
These are not for your victorious return.
One thousand five hundred years ago,
I was just an orchid in Arbiter Hall.
My master, Arbiter,
accidentally destroyed my immortal root,
so she didn't want to keep me.
Coincidentally,
you came to the Arbiter Hall
and persuaded my master to keep me,
saying maybe I can survive.
That's why I could cultivate my wisdom
and transform into human form.
So?
So…
So I want to tell you in person…
No. So…
So Lord Changheng,
you're my savior.
I've always wanted to thank you in person.
These flowers
are for you.
There's no need.
I don't remember
what you said.
You don't remember?
I'm sorry to bother you, Lord Changheng.
Wait.
Lord Changheng, your Spirit Jade.
You've already scared the fireflies away.
The Magical Firefly Stone
is just an ordinary stone.
It's useless to keep it.
Get rid of it for me.
You mean
you're giving it to me?
Not only did he give me a Spirit Jade,
but he also accepted my flower.
There were so many flowers,
but he just chose a little orchid.
Is this destiny?
What is this?
Lord Changheng!
I'll surely pass the immortal examination.
I will definitely enter
the Fountain Palace!
YUJING, SHUIYUNTIAN
IMMORTAL EXAMINATION PARTICIPANTS
As long as we can pass
the immortal examination,
we can serve Lord Changheng
in Fountain Palace.
We'll get the highest wage,
progress in rank rapidly,
and even see Lord Changheng often.
Yes. Right.
It's okay. There's a next time.
Isn't she a flower spirit?
Why is she here?
Exactly.
- Why is she here?
- Exactly.
How did she come in?
- How can she be here?
- Right.
- What good is she?
- She was chosen, I'm telling you…
- All right.
ARBITER HALL, ORCHID
- Why is she here?
- If she can pass, we'll all pass.
The lowest plant spirit
even wants to enter Fountain Palace?
- Exactly.
- How delusional.
I'm not that.
I remember her.
She's a peony by the gate of Arbiter Hall.
- No. She's a Bengal rose.
- Why is a peony here?
- What?
- I remember she's a peony.
- Is she a peony?
- Why is a little spirit here?
Even she can be here.
I'm neither a peony
nor a Bengal rose.
I am Orchid from Arbiter Hall.
All of you
had better remember
my name and background.
Because I will defeat all of you
in the immortal examination.
This…
- What a joke.
- Indeed.
- Look.
- What flower is she?
- Defeat us?
- Orchid.
What a joke!
How could they laugh at you?
Isn't it just the immortal examination?
If you fail, they may fail too.
Exactly. Whatever they've said,
you should just forget it.
We're all with you.
With friends like you,
it's worth it.
To be honest,
I do need
your support now.
As you all know,
my immortal root is damaged.
To pass the exam,
I have to cure it.
But elixirs
really cost a lot.
If you have any extra money,
can you…
PLANT SPIRIT, CREEPER
PLANT SPIRIT, PEACH
Peach.
Orchid,
in the past 1,000 years,
you've taken so many elixirs
and spent all your salary on that.
I think you'd better save your money.
PLANT SPIRIT, SUCCULENT
Yes. Exactly.
That's not what you said earlier.
I must repay Lord Changheng
for his kindness.
That has always been my dream.
For what?
You just like him.
We didn't want to expose your lie.
But you can't lie to yourself.
No matter how much you like him,
he won't like you.
Why?
You should know who your competitor is.
Danyin,
the most beautiful girl in Shuiyuntian.
Her father is Supreme Liyuan.
Who's your father?
Who?
Orchid.
You are a little flower.
You don't have a father.
What does this have to do with that?
Look.
This is called Magical Firefly Stone.
I've looked it up.
It is a rare jade.
In the cold Northernmost Ocean,
it takes 10,000 years for one to form.
It's extremely precious.
But Lord Changheng gave this to me.
Isn't this just a lame stone?
Maybe he was just tired of it
and didn't want it anymore.
Look.
The fireflies in it are all gone.
It's worthless.
Orchid.
We should accept our fates.
Stop dreaming. Just forget it.
Yes.
Enough!
Is what you're all saying
really for her sake?
Are you really Orchid's friends?
Friends should stand with her
at critical moments, shouldn't they?
Orchid, the spirit stones I've saved
are all in the garden.
I was going to buy some medicine
after transforming.
But now,
you can take them all.
Creeper, thank you.
By the way,
their private stashes
are there too.
Creeper, you wench!
- Orchid!
- No!
- Don't take mine.
- That's mine!
No words can express my thanks.
After I pass the immortal examination
and become an immortal maid,
my salary will be your salary!
This is great.
With these spirit stones,
I can buy elixirs.
That is Lord Changheng's Destiny Book.
How strange. The destiny
of a high immortal is very stable.
Why would it change?
Why did it break?
This is bad.
Lord Changheng's body and spirit
might be destroyed tonight.
HAOTIAN TOWER, SHUIYUNTIAN
It's time.
Immortals.
We have to strengthen the seal
within 15 minutes.
No mistake is allowed.
- Yes.
I've always been doing good deeds
and didn't do anything evil.
I don't wish to be rich or lucky.
I only hope I can fix my immortal root
and have a peaceful life.
My spirit won't dissipate today, right?
It's okay.
With so many high immortals,
Lord Changheng will surely be fine.
The lifeline of Lord Changheng
is still broken.
This looks exactly the same
as what I saw in the Destiny Book.
What should I do?
It's almost midnight.
My dear disciple, remember this.
The master of Destiny Books
can neither say anything to its owner
nor change anyone's fate.
Otherwise, he will bear
the wrath of the heavens
and his spirit will dissipate.
Changheng!
Lord Yunzhong.
A fairy has fallen into Haotian Tower.
The seal of Haotian Tower
has been completed.
We can't open it again.
Help!
DONGFANG QINGCANG'S SEA OF EMOTIONS
Who is she?
Why is she wearing my dress?
A ghost!
Help!
Help me.
Let go of me.
Help.
Shut up.
Why do you look like me?
I don't know
why I have switched bodies with you.
You mean
you are now in my body
and I'm in yours?
Then what should we do?
Do you see the Haotian Matrix?
That is the exit.
As you are in my body,
you now have mighty power.
As long as you destroy the matrix
with your power,
we can break the seal and escape.
After we go out,
we can naturally switch our bodies back.
The Haotian Matrix?
Wait.
You are a criminal who was sealed.
You want to trick me into letting you out.
You'd better not mention me
in the same breath as those losers.
My patience is limited.
Destroy the Haotian Matrix now.
Otherwise,
I'll kill you now.